https://www.map.org/privacy-policy-new/

Privacy Policy
We honor the trust you place in us to steward your generous gifts.
MAP International Donor Privacy Policy
MAP International has the following privacy policy in place to help maintain your trust and to protect the personal information you provide to us. Outlined below is our privacy policy for any and all donor and partner information collected through all outlets. If you have questions about these policies, we encourage you to contact us.
No Resale of Information to Third Parties
MAP International does not exchange, trade, sell, or rent donor information with anyone else, nor send donor mailings on behalf of other organizations. All personal information obtained from donors or key stakeholders, including names, addresses, phone numbers and or e-mails are held in strict confidence.  Only MAP International and its authorized agents have access to personally identifiable information provided by our donors and partners. Constituents may choose to have personal information removed from MAP International records by calling us at 912-265-6010 or contacting us.
Opt-Out
MAP International provides users with the ability to opt-out of any and all communications in accordance with the CAN-SPAM act and other relevant laws. Users can choose to opt-out of all communications by following any of the methods below:
Contact us online and indicate that you'd like to opt-out of MAP International communications.
Call us at 912-265-6010
Send us a request via postal mail to: MAP International4700 Glynco ParkwayBrunswick, GA 31525
When contacting us, please be sure to include any information that will help us identify you in our database, such as full name, home address and/or email address.
Protecting Your Information
MAP takes reasonable precautions to protect our users' information and is certified to be Trustwave-PCI compliant per the attached certificate. All account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we never send private information by email or instant messaging services.
Although we allow privacy setting that limit access to information, we are aware that no security measures are perfect or 100 percent effective but strive to maintain all current and reasonable safeguards for client and donor information. MAP is committed to protecting consumer credit card data in compliance with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS). Our alignment with this standard is reflected in the people, technologies and processes we employ. We conduct regular vulnerability scans and penetration tests in accordance with the PCI DSS requirements for our business model.
Return Policy & Quality Control
If you experience any difficulties or notice any errors when making a donation to MAP International, please call MAP International at 912-265-6010 or contact us here as soon as possible.  MAP International is committed to serving your charitable needs to your satisfaction.  If your donation was made in error and you need a refund, please notify MAP immediately. Refunds will be granted for 45 days after a donation is made.
Improving Customer Service
As with any website operator, MAP International partner organizations analyze our website logs to constantly improve the value of our website. We use an external service to provide real-time reporting to us and our authorized agents of browser accesses to our site. This reporting includes page views, unique views, unique visitors, repeat visitors, frequency of visits, and peak-volume traffic periods. We do not use this service to gather, request, record, require, collect or track any Internet users' personally identifiable information.
Personalization of Content
We use cookies on our site to personalize the experience of our visitors and to support some necessary functions. We also use cookies to better understand how our visitors use our site. You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. However, please note that if you reject some or all cookies, your experience at this and on other sites throughout the Internet may not be complete. In addition, if you do not allow cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of personalized content delivery offered by other Internet sites or by us.
Communicating With You
MAP International partner organizations maintain several e-mail lists to keep our supporters, the press and policy makers informed about news and events.
Individuals who provide optional information may also receive materials in the U.S. mail and/or be contacted by telephone by MAP International. In addition, we do not share the personal information on our lists with staff outside of MAP partner organizations and their authorized agents. We configure our list server software to refuse to divulge the personal information of our list subscribers to anyone but authorized MAP partner organization staff and agents. Only MAP partner organization staff and our authorized agents have access to personally identifiable information provided by our donors and partners.
Protecting Children
Because we care about the safety and privacy of children online, we comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying FTC regulation establish United States federal law that protects the privacy of children using the Internet. We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. Our site is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under 13, and we have designed our site to block our knowing acceptance of information from children under 13 whenever age-related information is requested.
It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the notification, we will immediately obtain parental consent or otherwise delete the information from our servers. If you want to notify us of our receipt of information by children under 13, please contact us.
Maintaining Security
We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving financial data from our site. In addition, we have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss or misuse of information at our site that we have collected from you.
A History of Trust
Since our founding we have been known as an organization that delivers quality medicines to those in need with remarkably low overhead.
For donors like you, this means we do the most good with each dollar you give.
In 2019, we helped over 13 million people by providing millions of healing doses of medicines. We did this all with a staff of fewer than 50 people in our U.S offices and warehouse.
We are able to deliver so much medicine at low cost because pharmaceutical companies donate many of the products we send overseas.
These are unexpired medicines that are desperately needed by people in many parts of the world. We also purchase medicines when necessary to meet specific needs.
We find MAP International to be professionally managed and a leader in their industry. MAP ranks in the top 5 percent of our clients in quality of financial reporting, management & board leadership.”– Daniel M. Campbell, CapinCrouse LLP
PRIVACY POLICY
Donate to the General Fund
Become a Blue Box Member
Donate to Disaster Relief
Purchase from our Gift Catalog
Give
Partners
Media
MAP International is a registered 501c3 non-profit organization. All donations to MAP International (EIN: 36-2586390) are tax-deductible.
